tripnmate.com 2016-04-06

# Tripnmate - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

We respect the confidentiality of your information.

What information do we record? We will request for you to voluntarily give us information from time to time. In general, this information is required is you sign up for this online service or you require information for an online transaction.

**How do we use this information?**

Your e-mail address is solely used for the official purposes of Tripnmate.com and under no circumstances is disclosed to any third party organization. We could use your phone number to contact you urgently (e.g. if the wrong e-mail address was entered).

Your credit card or other transaction is not stored in our database. Neither we have access to your Transaction information during a transaction. Tripnmate.com contain links to other websites. We take no responsibility for the data security or the content of these websites.

We use "Cookies“to record areas of the site which are of particular interest to you.

Tripnmate reserves the right to hire third parties to perform studies such market research and to provide the data which are necessary to perform these studies. These data are then used exclusively for this project and are protected by the Confidentiality Agreement.

Opt out of Newsletter you can opt out of our Newsletter at any time. You will find the instructions on this in the Newsletter. You can also send an e-mail to [newsletter@tripnmate.com](mailto:newsletter@tripnmate.com).

**Use of your Personal data**

Your Personal data stored with the web portal is or will be used but not restricted for the following purposes,

  * For the services or to support your request;
  * To contact you from time to time with user or service updates;
  * To send other messages that help us provide our services on the Site;
  * To assist people you have done business with.
  * To customize, measure, report on and improve our services, content and advertising;
  * To promote services related to the Site
  * To compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties;
  * To prevent, investigate or prosecute activity we think may be potentially illegal, unlawful or harmful and
  * To enforce our Privacy Policy and/or our Terms or any other purpose referenced herein or therein.

We collate statistics about site traffic, sales and other commercial information which we pass onto third parties to assist us in improving the services we provide to you. We also use demographic information to tailor the Site and we share that information with third parties so that they can build up a better picture of our customer base and general consumer trends.

How We May Disclose Your Personal Data We may disclose your personal data to enforce our policies, or where we are permitted to do so by applicable law, such as in response to a request by a law enforcement or governmental authority, or in connection with actual or proposed litigation, or to protect our property, people and other rights or interests.

**We may also share your personal data with:**

  * One of our partners if you've requested their services or if you’ve requested to be provided with information by them;
  * Another member if you have done business with them;
  * A third party performing services on our behalf; 
  * Companies in the Tripnmate stays Group and/or affiliates; or
  * Other companies or business entities, for example if we are thinking of a merger with or sale to that company or business entity; or
  * Any third party you have asked us to share your personal data with – such as Facebook if you have asked us to connect with your Facebook account.

You may have accessed our website through a hyperlink from the website of one of our trading partners. If so, you consent to your personal details and purchase information, including behavioral patterns, being shared with that trading partner in accordance with our contractual relationship with them.

In the unlikely event that we or Tripnmate or any part of the Tripnmate group is sold, or some of its assets transferred to a third party, your personal information, as a valuable asset, may also be transferred. Potential purchasers and their advisors may have access to data as part of the sale process. However, use of your personal information will remain subject to this Privacy Policy. Similarly, your personal information may be passed on to a successor in interest in the unlikely event of a liquidation, bankruptcy, or administration. Our customer database could be sold separately from the rest of the business, in whole or in a number of parts. It could be that the purchaser's business is different from ours, too. Personal Information Protection

Unless otherwise provided within these Terms, or unless specific applicable law requires TRIPNMATE.COM to allow you to do so, you may not do any of the following without the prior written consent of TRIPNMATE.COM: Copy, reproduce, upload, post, display, republish, distribute, transmit, any part of the Content in any form whatsoever

Reproduce our content on your Web site using any device including, but not limited to, use of a frame or border environment around the Web site, or other framing technique to enclose any portion or aspect of the Web site, or mirror or replicate any portion of the Site; Modify, translate into any language or computer language, or create derivative works from, any Content or any part of this Web site;

Reverse engineer any part of this Web site; Use any robot, spider, other automatic device, or manual process to monitor, copy, or keep a database copy of the Content; Use the Web site other than to browse or submit listings; Use the Web site to make any false or fraudulent activity; Post or transmit any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, indecent, inflammatory, pornographic or profane material or any material that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any law; or for any other purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms; Use or access the Web site in any way that, in our reasonable judgment, adversely affects the performance or function of the Site, or any other computer systems or networks used by TRIPNMATE, or infringes on our copyright or the copyright of our advertisers; Upload or transmit to the Web site or use any device, software or routine that contains viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, or other computer programming routines that may damage, interfere or attempt to interfere with, intercept, the normal operation of our Web site, or appropriate the Web site or any system, or take any action that imposes an unreasonable load on our computer equipment, or that infringes upon the rights of a third party; Use any device, software, or routine that interferes, or attempts to interfere, with the normal operation of our site, or take any action that impose an unreasonable load on our equipment; or appropriate the Web site or any system, or take any action that imposes an unreasonable load on our computer equipment, or that infringes upon the rights of a third party; Use any device, software, or routine that interferes, or attempts to interfere, with the normal operation of our site, or take any action that impose an unreasonable load on our equipment; or Disguise the origin of the information transmitted through the Web site.

#### **Cookies**

Cookies are used to enhance users experience and this technology is used by most up to date Websites. You may delete and block all cookies from this site, but parts of the site will not work. Even if you are only browsing the Site certain information (including computer and connection information, browser type and version, operating system and platform details, and the time of accessing the Site) is automatically collected about you. This information is collected every time you access the Site and it will be used for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy.

#### **Phishing or False emails**

If you receive an unsolicited email that appears to be from us or one of our members that requests personal information (such as your credit card, login, or password), or that asks you to verify or confirm your account or other personal information by clicking on a link, that email was likely to have been sent by someone trying to unlawfully obtain your information, sometimes referred to as a "phisher" or "spoofer." We do not ask for this type of information in an email. Do not provide the information or click on the link. Validity of personal data?

We will retain your personal data only as long as is necessary for the purposes to which you consent under the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy, or as is required by applicable law, and then we will delete it.

Any suggestions or complains? If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, we encourage you to contact us at [support@tripnmate.com](mailto:support@tripnmate.com), If you are unhappy with their answer you can write to our Chief Privacy Officer at [rahul.chadha@tripnmate.com](mailto:rahul.chadha@tripnmate.com).

Or Write us at - 

###### Head Office: 

**vdream solutions pvt ltd**  
356A High Streeet North, Manor Park, London  
E12 6PH  
United Kingdom 

\- Or - 

**vdream solutions pvt ltd**  
perth level 18, QBE House  
200 St Georges Terrace Perth  
WA 6000  
Australia
